clickmagick.com 2019-07-19

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy  
We're serious about online privacy, and have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. This page outlines our information gathering and dissemination practices, and our use of user information and Personal Data.What information does ClickMagick collect from visitors and users?

ClickMagick collects information from users of our website - including Personal Data - and uses the information for marketing, security and administration purposes, in the fulfillment of our service commitment to you, or as required by law.

By voluntarily providing Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In doing so you also acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your location to the offices and servers of ClickMagick anywhere in the world.

We will keep any Personal Data that you provide to us indefinitely unless you cancel your ClickMagick account and/or specifically request that we permanently delete your Personal Data.

Why is information collected?

Information may be collected in an effort to enhance your user experience, provide you with information regarding ClickMagick services or other related special offers, and/or to provide you with the products and/or services that you request or purchase from us.

Most commonly, we collect your Personal Data when you voluntarily provide it by creating a ClickMagick account. We use this Personal Data that you provide when creating an account to provide access to the ClickMagick service, as well as for security and billing purposes.

We, or our authorized third-party affiliates, may also collect aggregate information about transactions as they correspond to our advertisements, products and services. This aggregate information may include various types of demographic and usage information, but 

_does not include Personal Data_.

This information is used in an aggregated manner to determine advertising effectiveness and is sometimes shared with our advertising partners for the same limited purpose.

How does ClickMagick protect my information?

We've implemented a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your Personal Data. Personal Data is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by key employees.

Should it be necessary to transmit your Personal Data to a third party to fulfill our service commitment to you, ClickMagick will require all recipients of Personal Data to maintain it as confidential, use the information for the limited and intended purpose and agree not to disclose such information.

Will ClickMagick disclose the information it collects to others?

ClickMagick does not sell or share any of the data collected by this site with unrelated 3rd-parties, except to provide the products or services you've requested, or under the following circumstances:

  * We respond to subpoenas or court orders, or to establish or exercise our legal rights;
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action in conjunction with illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ClickMagick's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.  

Does ClickMagick use Cookies or Pixel Tags?

Cookies allow website owners to better customize a site to your individual preferences and provide a better experience, and we use cookies for this purpose.

Please note however that 

_we do not store Personal Data in cookies_.

Like many websites, ClickMagick may also use pixel tags to improve our understanding of site traffic, visitor behavior, and response to promotional and advertising campaigns, as a supplement to our server logs and other methods of traffic and response measurement.

We may also use pixel tags provided by 3rd-parties, and limit the collection of information for the same purpose. 

_We do not store Personal Data in pixel tags_.Can I Access, Modify or Delete the Personal Data ClickMagick collects?

Absolutely. You can view and/or modify the Personal Data that you've provided to us at any time by logging in to your ClickMagick account, and clicking the "Profile" link.

You may also submit your request to access, view, or modify your account information - or to permanently delete it from our servers and databases - at any time via any of the methods below.

What information does ClickMagick collect from Customers' Users?

As a user of the ClickMagick service, you should be aware that depending on how you use the service we may collect Personal Data from your website visitors and customers.

By default the only Personal Data we may collect from your users is the IP address of their request(s) at the time that they interact with the ClickMagick system. We collect IP addresses for the sole purpose of ensuring accuracy of the ClickMagick service, and for security purposes.

The IP addresses of your website visitors and customers are not shared with any third-parties, so there are no privacy or security issues related to the collection of this Personal Data.

However, based on how you're using the ClickMagick service you may be sending to us and causing us to store other Personal Data such as your user's name, billing information or email address.

We will always do our best to use encryption and other technologies to ensure that your customer's Personal Data that you send to us is safe and secure, but please remember that you're responsible for gathering any applicable consents for data collection when users visit your website.

In regards to General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR), ClickMagick is the "data processor" and the ClickMagick customer is the "data controller", as such terms are defined under the GDPR.

The data controller collects data from our data subjects (i.e., a customer's end users) and says how and why personal data is processed. The data processor receives the data from the data controller and acts upon instructions from the data controller.

We understand the GDPR has robust requirements and obligations for both data collectors and data processors and we're committed to helping our customers use ClickMagick in a GDPR compliant manner. We've made our Data Processing Addendum (DPA) available online so that our customers can be confident that their data is processed in a lawful manner.

What if I want to Opt-Out of email communications from ClickMagick?

ClickMagick provides every user with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future promotional communications from us. You may do so in the following ways.

Please note however that even if you opt-out, you may still receive announcements or updates regarding your ClickMagick account unless you cancel your account.

1\. Email: help@clickmagick.com  
  
2\. Website: https://www.clickmagick.com/contact.cgi  
  
3\. Telephone: 213-761-4681 (if you're having trouble with the above)  
  
4\. Postal Mail: ClickMagick Inc., 12333 Sowden Rd Ste B #66217, Houston, TX 77080

Can children or minors use ClickMagick?

ClickMagick does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from or about anyone under the age of 13. If we discover we've received such information, we will delete that information immediately.

If you believe ClickMagick has any information about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us. If you are under 13, you may use ClickMagick only under the supervision of a parent or guardian.

Third-Party Payment Processor

We use [Stripe](https://www.stripe.com/), one of the Internet's largest third-party payment processors, to manage ClickMagick subscriptions and to process payments made to ClickMagick.

When you create a ClickMagick account, your personal financial information including your credit card number and billing address are securely transmitted directly to Stripe for processing, and ClickMagick has no record of it whatsoever.

The manner in which Stripe uses, stores and discloses your information is governed by their own published privacy, security and other policies, and ClickMagick has no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Stripe.

With that being said, you can rest assured that your Personal Data is safe with Stripe. As one of the Internet's largest payment processors - processing billions of dollars worth of transactions per year - their privacy and security practices are second to none.

Links to Other Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to the ClickMagick website, and your dealings with ClickMagick.

This website does however contain links to other websites, and we want you to know that ClickMagick is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites.

We encourage users to be aware when they leave the ClickMagick website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects Personal Data.

Updates to this Privacy Policy

The ClickMagick service may change from time to time, and as a result it may be necessary for us to make changes to this Privacy Policy, which we reserve the right to do at any time.

Should this be necessary we'll post any changes here so that you're always aware of the information that we collect and how we intend to use it. We will also alert you via an in-app notification and/or via email if and when this Privacy Policy is updated, so you're always kept up to date.

ClickMagick Terms of Service

There's just one more thing we want you to know - your access to and use of the ClickMagick service is also subject to the Terms of Service located at <https://www.clickmagick.com/terms.cgi>.

Contacting ClickMagick

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy-related practices of this website please contact us via one of the methods above.

This Privacy Policy was last updated May 5th, 2018.
